mypresta.eu 2017-06-06

# Cookies and privacy policy

###  Cookies & privacy policy 

To buy a part of our Services (order process / paid software and services) you need to provide us your personal information. Your privacy is the most important thing to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we collects, and the ways in which we use your personal informations.

**Data that you will provide here are processed by:**

VEKIA  
66-100 Sulechow  
Wisniowa 34 street  
POLAND  
VAT-EU PL9730945634

**Personal information collection:   **

We may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information about all transactions carried out over this website;
  * Any other information that you send to us, like first name, last name, address, e-mail address and phone numbers.

**Using personal information:   **

All data that you will provide will not be sold anywhere, and they will be used only for order purposes (invoices for order). So these informations can be used:

  1. to collect and identify payments from you;
  2. to send you digital products that you purchased;
  3. to send you information about order status and creating account process (register)
  4. to generate and send an invoice for the order

**Cookies Policy:  ** 

This website uses cookies to handle informations about you. It is necessary for the proper functioning of the store.

  1. We use Google Analytics cookies to handle informations about your actions on our store to improve our site usability.
  2. We use Zopim - Support Chat cookies to improve our support for you. 
  3. In addition, we also use standard session cookies to hold informations about your cart / order / customer account.

Remember that you can disable cookies in your web browser settings.
